No way back, one way out.
John Wick: Chapter 4 is a action, thriller, crime
film directed by Chad Stahelski.
With the price on his head ever increasing, John Wick
uncovers a path to defeating The High Table.
But before he can earn his freedom, Wick must face off against a new enemy with powerful
alliances across the globe and forces that turn old friends into foes.
John Wick, played by Keanu Reeves.
Caine, played by Donnie Yen.
Marquis, played by Bill Skarsgård.
Winston, played by Ian McShane.
Bowery King, played by Laurence Fishburne.
Charon, played by Lance Reddick.
John Wick: Chapter 4 is a 2023 American neo-noir action thriller film, directed and
co-produced by Chad Stahelski and written by Shay Hatten and Michael Finch.
It is the fourth installment in the John Wick film series, and the
sequel to John Wick: Chapter 3 – Parabellum (2019).
Keanu Reeves returns as the titular John Wick, who sets out for
revenge on the High Table and those who left him for dead.
Chapter 4 also features Donnie Yen, Bill Skarsgård, Laurence Fishburne, Hiroyuki Sanada, Shamier
Anderson, Lance Reddick, Rina Sawayama, Scott Adkins, Clancy Brown, and Ian McShane.
Development of the fourth John Wick film, formally announced by Lionsgate in
May 2019, was confirmed before the release of its predecessor.
It is the first film in the franchise that was not written by franchise creator
Derek Kolstad; Hatten was hired in May 2020, then Finch in March 2021.
Principal photography took place from June to October 2021 in
France, Germany, New York City, and Japan.
The film's planned 2021 release was delayed by the COVID-19 pandemic.
John Wick: Chapter 4 premiered at the Odeon Luxe Leicester Square in London on
March 6, 2023, and was released in the United States on March 24.
The film received critical acclaim from critics, who praised its action sequences, Stahelski's
direction, cinematography, choreography, visual style, writing, score, and performances.
It earned $447.3 million worldwide, on a $100 million budget,
becoming the highest-grossing film in the franchise.
A spin-off set between the third and fourth films,
titled Ballerina, was released in 2025.
Though Chapter 4 was initially intended to be the conclusion
of the series, a sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of new york city, martial
arts, berlin, germany, hitman, sequel.
The tone is dark and intense.